<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Findings on Virginia Tech</title>
    <link>/findings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Findings on Virginia Tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/findings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Findings 1</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-one/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3 { text-align: center; }  Modeling Census Tract Level Evictions: Correlates Of Eviction Rates The following variables were significantly associated with census tract level evictions.
Socio-demographic:
 Percentage of tract that is Black or African American (+), Percentage of tract aged 16+ who are unemployed (+), Census tract poverty rate (+), Percentage of tract with a bachelor’s degree (-),  State policy factors:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Findings 2</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-two/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3 { text-align: center; }  Modeling Census Tract Level Evictions : Richmond: Visualizing An Index Of Eviction Intensity The Eviction Intensity Index we created from our regression model was used to rank all census tracts in U.S. cities that are comparable in size to Richmond in the United States. The wordcloud below visualizes the frequency that census tracts with the words “Richmond City” show up in a list of the top 320 most eviction intense tracts in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Findings 3</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-three/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3 { text-align: center; }  Modeling Census Tract Level Evictions: Visualization of socio-demographic variables and eviction rates in Richmond 2013-2018 To provide further guidance for policymakers interested in understanding evictions in Richmond, we provide a dashboard that can be used to visualize the socio-demographic variables that our statistical model identified as being associated with eviction rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conclusion</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-four/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3 { text-align: center; }  We determined that state level landlord and tenant friendly policies are significantly associated with tract level eviction rates. These finding suggested that state level policy levers such as:
 Laws that protected class exemptions in housing-related transactions, Laws that protect tenants from retaliation by landlords Laws that reduce the number of exemptions landlords have from state landlord-tenant law  can affect evictions rates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>References</title>
      <link>/findings/references/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/references/</guid>
      <description>Eviction Lab Data Downloads. (2018). Retrieved July 30, 2020, from https://eviction-lab-data-downloads.s3.amazonaws.com/DATA_DICTIONARY.txt
Missouri Census Data Center. (2018). Retrieved July 30, 2020, from http://mcdc.missouri.edu/applications/geocorr2018.html
Eviction Lab Data: Matthew Desmond, Ashley Gromis, Lavar Edmonds, James Hendrickson, Katie Krywokulski, Lillian Leung, and Adam Porton. Eviction Lab National Database: Version 1.0. Princeton: Princeton University, 2018, www.evictionlab.org.
Washington, Lark. “Rehouse Richmond: Plan to Address the Eviction Crisis.” (2020).
Desmond, Matthew. 2012 “Eviction and the reproduction of urban poverty.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>