<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Virginia Tech</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Virginia Tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Eviction Rate Regression Model</title>
      <link>/findings/general-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/general-overview/</guid>
      <description>Main Findings Compared to the reference population as described in Data and Methodology, estimates of a unit increase in the following variables were associated with increases in the squared root eviction rate:
 The number of protected class exemptions in housing-related transactions in state law and 0.3935, Whether tenants in the state are protected from retaliation by landlords after asserting their legal rights and 0.2037, Number of exemptions landlords have from state landlord-tenant law and 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results Section One</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-one/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3 { text-align: center; }  Examples Page If you want to add in an image on an Rmd file, use this link here. It ends up being a little tricky, but as long as you have created a folder to insert your images, you can just use some markdown code or html to insert images in the format you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results Section Two</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-two/</guid>
      <description>[Here you will describe the data discoversy process, the data used, and the methods employed for this single page. Since you already have a Project Overview and Data &amp;amp; Methods tabs, you probably want to keep this first paragraph fairly short and use the rest of the document to walk your readers through your analyses.]
Main Findings [Here you will describe the results and include important visualizations from your project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results Section Three</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-three/</guid>
      <description>[Here you will describe the data discoversy process, the data used, and the methods employed for this single page. Since you already have a Project Overview and Data &amp;amp; Methods tabs, you probably want to keep this first paragraph fairly short and use the rest of the document to walk your readers through your analyses.]
Main Findings [Here you will describe the results and include important visualizations from your project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/methods/</guid>
      <description>2020 Richmond City Summer Project Data and Methodology This research uses data from The Eviction Lab at Princeton University, a project directed by Matthew Desmond and designed by Ashley Gromis, Lavar Edmonds, James Hendrickson, Katie Krywokulski, Lillian Leung, and Adam Porton. The Eviction Lab is funded by the JPB, Gates, and Ford Foundations as well as the Chan Zuckerberg Initiative. More information is found at evictionlab.org. For our primary data source, we used the Eviction Lab’s records on evictions at the 2010 census tract level for all cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/overview/</guid>
      <description>2020 Richmond City Project The city of Richmond has one of the highest eviction rates in the United States.
Project Goals This project aims to help Virginia Cooperative Extension (VCE) carefully target their nutrition and financial literacy programs to the areas of highest need within the city of Richmond.
Our Approach The VT-DSPG program partnered with VCE to first identify the factors that predict eviction. Then used this information to develop an eviction vulnerability index which maps socio-economic determinants of eviction at the census tract level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/team_ref/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team_ref/</guid>
      <description>UVA Data Science for the Public Good Program The Data Science for the Public Good (DSPG) Young Scholars program is a summer immersive program held at the Biocomplexity Institute’s Social and Decision Analytics division (SDAD). In its seventh year, the program engages students from across the country to work together on projects that address state, federal, and local government challenges around critical social issues relevant in the world today. DSPG young scholars conduct research at the intersection of statistics, computation, and the social sciences to determine how information generated within every community can be leveraged to improve quality of life and inform public policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> </title>
      <link>/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/</guid>
      <description>Data Science for the Public Good Program  The Data Science for the Public Good (DSPG) Young Scholars program(https://biocomplexity.virginia.edu/social-decision-analytics/dspg-program) is a summer immersive program held at the Biocomplexity Institute’s Social and Decision Analytics division (SDAD). In its seventh year, the program engages students from across the country to work together on projects that address state, federal, and local government challenges around critical social issues relevant in the world today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>test</title>
      <link>/findings/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/test/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>